

AGUNG PRIYADI

SOFTWARE QA

About Me

Let me introduce myself, my name is Agung Priyadi. Born in Tangerang, May 08 1997. I live on JI Keramat Raya Bencongan Indah No 38 Tangerang. Recent experience working as QA Software at Bank Mandiri.

Personality

- Hard woker
- Teamwork/ Alone
- Communicative

Contact

Telepon

085714309386

Email

agung.priyadi96@gmail.com

Address

Jl Keramat Raya Bencongan Indah No 38 Tangerang

Language

English Indonesia

Education

2003-2009 *SDN Perumnas 02*

2009-2012 *SMP Pgri 400*

2012-2015 *SMK Yuppentek 7*

2015-2019 Universitas Raharja (S1 - Teknik Informatika

Experience

PT Fans Indonesia 2018-2019 IT Staff

PT Sumber Alfaria Trijaya Tbk 2020-2021 Admin Gudang
PT Pancamitra 2022-2022 Desain Grafis

Bank Mandiri 2023-2023 Software Quality Assurance

Testing banking application and web application

- Create testing scenario (positive, negative)
- Execute all testing scenario and create documentation for the results
- Distribute bugs to programmers
- Monitor bugs handling and perform rechecking
- Make documentation for each activity of testing
- Implementation all scenario testing with users at User Acceptance Test (UAT)

Skill

Testing Software Web Applications, Android Applications
Creating Test Scenarios (Positive and Negative Tests)
Execute testing scenarios and create testing documentation
Perform Application Analysis and Find Bugs and deficiencies in the application
Understand and familiar with JIRA

Can Use AS 400 Software

Understand PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, CI, Boostraps, Wordpress Able to Operate Microsoft Office and Corel Draw